{
    "id": "76_Entertainment_647",
    "claim": "The team of Jose Antonio Meade, candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico, continues to think of ways to position him in the race for the presidency, despite the fact that he is lagging behind in a distant third place in all the polls (behind Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador and Ricardo Anaya) and that it is less than a month before the elections. The most recent idea is to include it in the famous series of Luis Miguel, in Netflix. To do this, the PRI has offered the producers  millions of dollars to modify the chapters that remain to be transmitted. In the proposed story to modify the argument will be included the character of Jose Antonio Meade, who in the late eighties will be a young but intelligent economist who also serves as a private detective. Luis Miguel will hire him not only to find his mother, but also to expose his father, Luisito Rey, and all his evils. The candidate's team wants to film a scene where Meade gives Luisito Rey a sovereign beating, making him disappear from his son's life.'You have won this time, but I will return!'will King tell him, before throwing a smoke bomb to disappear into the shadows. At the end of the chapter, Luisito Rey will arrive at his secret lair, where he will meet his boss, The Tabasque√±o Messiah, who will kill him for not being able to stop Meade. They also want to modify the end of the series, so that it will be located in the present and be a concert of Luis Miguel in the closing of Meade's campaign. There is still no response from producers. I'm sorry.",
    "source": "www.eldizque.com",
    "date": "05/06/2018",
    "veracity": 0,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "The team of Jose Antonio Meade, candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico , continues to think of ways to position Jose Antonio Meade, candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico in the race for the presidency, despite the fact that Jose Antonio Meade, candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico is lagging behind in a distant third place in all the polls (behind Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador and Ricardo Anaya) and that it is less than a month before the elections.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is Jose Antonio Meade?",
                    "answer": "candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many polls did Jose Antonio Meade receive in the 2018 election?",
                    "score": 0.8335,
                    "answers": "in a distant third place in all the polls ( behind Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador and Ricardo Anaya|prep\tall the polls ( behind Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador and Ricardo Anaya|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many votes does Jose Antonio Meade have for the presidency?",
                    "score": 0.7963,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com reported on 05/06/2018 that The team of Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico , continues to think of ways to position Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico in the race for the presidency , despite the fact that Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico is lagging behind in a distant third place in all the polls ( behind Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador and Ricardo Anaya ) and that it is less than a month before the elections|ROOT\tthat|mark\tThe|det\t,|punct\tthe|det\t,|punct\tto|aux\tto|aux\t,|punct\tthe|det\tthe|det\tthe race for the presidency|pobj\tthe|det\t,|punct\tthe|det\tthat|mark\t,|punct\tthe|det\tis|aux\ta|det\tthe|det\t(|punct\tand|cc\t)|punct\tand|cc\tthat|mark\tit|nsubj\tless|amod\tthan|quantmod\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the polling for Meade's candidacy for the presidency?",
                    "score": 0.7654,
                    "answers": "ways to position Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico in the race for the presidency , despite the fact that Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico is lagging behind in a distant third place in all the polls ( behind Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador and Ricardo Anaya ) and that it is less than a month before the elections|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Jose Antonio Meade's polling numbers for the presidency?",
                    "score": 0.7567,
                    "answers": "that it is less than a month before the elections|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Jose Antonio Meade running for?",
                    "score": 0.7261,
                    "answers": "for Mexico|prep\tfor Mexico|prep\tfor the presidency|prep\tfor Mexico|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The most recent idea is to include Jose Antonio Meade, candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico in the famous series of Luis Miguel , in Netflix.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What famous series was Jose Antonio Meade in?",
                    "answer": "Luis Miguel"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What series did Jose Antonio Meade participate in?",
                    "score": 0.8635,
                    "answers": "in the famous series of Luis Miguel|prep\tfamous|amod\tthe famous series of Luis Miguel|pobj\tof Luis Miguel|prep\tLuis|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Jose Antonio Meade's political affiliation?",
                    "score": 0.7699,
                    "answers": "for Mexico|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the most recent idea for the Todos coalition for Mexico?",
                    "score": 0.7434,
                    "answers": "The most recent idea|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Jose Antonio Meade?",
                    "score": 0.7371,
                    "answers": "to include Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico in the famous series of Luis Miguel , in Netflix|xcomp\tJose|compound\tJose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico in the famous series of Luis Miguel|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Jose Antonio Meade and Luis Miguel?",
                    "score": 0.7266,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com|nsubj\twww.eldizque.com reported on 05/06/2018 that The most recent idea is to include Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico in the famous series of Luis Miguel , in Netflix|ROOT\ton 05/06/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tThe|det\tmost|advmod\tmost recent|amod\tthat The most recent idea is to include Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico in the famous series of Luis Miguel , in Netflix|ccomp\tto|aux\tAntonio|compound\t,|punct\tcandidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico in the famous series of Luis Miguel|appos\tthe|det\tthe|det\t,|punct\tin Netflix|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "To do include , the PRI has offered the producers  millions of dollars to modify the chapters that remain to be transmitted.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did www.eldizque.com report that the PRI has offered the producers millions of dollars to modify the chapters that remain to be transmitted?",
                    "answer": "To do include"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How much money has the PRI offered producers to modify chapters?",
                    "score": 0.8207,
                    "answers": "  millions of dollars to modify the chapters that remain to be transmitted|dep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In the proposed story to modify the argument will be included Jose Antonio Meade, candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What coalition is Jose Antonio Meade a candidate for?",
                    "answer": "the Todos coalition"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Jose Antonio Meade's political affiliation?",
                    "score": 0.742,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com reported on 05/06/2018 that In the proposed story to modify the argument will be included Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico|ROOT\tIn the proposed story|prep\tthe proposed story|pobj\tfor Mexico|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Jose Antonio Meade?",
                    "score": 0.7187,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthe|det\tto|aux\tthe|det\tbe|auxpass\tthat In the proposed story to modify the argument will be included Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico|ccomp\tJose|compound\tAntonio|compound\tJose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico|nsubj\t,|punct\tcandidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico|appos\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the proposed story to modify the argument?",
                    "score": 0.689,
                    "answers": "to modify|advcl\tthe argument|nsubjpass"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the Todos coalition for Mexico?",
                    "score": 0.6795,
                    "answers": "of the Todos coalition for Mexico|prep\tthe Todos coalition for Mexico|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Luis Miguel will hire Jose Antonio Meade, candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico not only to find mother, but also to expose his father, Luisito Rey , and all evils.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is Jose Antonio Meade's father?",
                    "answer": "Luisito Rey"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did Luis Miguel hire Jose Antonio Meade as his father?",
                    "score": 0.9363,
                    "answers": "not only to find mother , but also to expose his father , Luisito Rey , and all evils|xcomp\tto expose his father , Luisito Rey , and all evils|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Luis Miguel's relationship with Luisito Rey?",
                    "score": 0.8087,
                    "answers": "his father , Luisito Rey , and all evils|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Luis Miguel and Luisito Rey?",
                    "score": 0.751,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com reported on 05/06/2018 that Luis Miguel will hire Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico not only to find mother , but also to expose his father , Luisito Rey , and all evils|ROOT\tthat Luis Miguel will hire Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico not only to find mother , but also to expose his father , Luisito Rey , and all evils|ccomp\tJose|compound\tof the Todos coalition for Mexico|prep\tLuisito|compound\tall evils|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Jose Antonio Meade?",
                    "score": 0.7418,
                    "answers": "Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The team of Jose Antonio Meade, candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico wants to film a scene where Jose Antonio Meade, candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico gives his father, Luisito Rey a sovereign beating, making his father, Luisito Rey disappear from Luis Miguel life.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the team of Jose Antonio Meade want to film?",
                    "answer": "gives his father, Luisito Rey a sovereign beating, making his father, Luisito Rey disappear"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did Jose Antonio Meade give his father a sovereign beating?",
                    "score": 0.7938,
                    "answers": "making his father , Luisito Rey disappear from Luis Miguel life|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Meade say about Luisito Rey?",
                    "score": 0.7737,
                    "answers": "that The team of Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico wants to film a scene where Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico gives his father , Luisito Rey a sovereign beating , making his father , Luisito Rey disappear from Luis Miguel life|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened to Jose Antonio Meade's father Luisito Rey?",
                    "score": 0.7405,
                    "answers": "a scene where Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico gives his father , Luisito Rey a sovereign beating , making his father , Luisito Rey disappear from Luis Miguel life|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was Luis Miguel's relationship with Jose Antonio Meade?",
                    "score": 0.7202,
                    "answers": "his father , Luisito Rey disappear from Luis Miguel life|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Jose Antonio Meade?",
                    "score": 0.6808,
                    "answers": "The team of Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico|nsubj\tof Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico|prep\tJose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico|pobj\tJose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "'You have won this time, but his father, Luisito Rey will return!'will King tell his father, Luisito Rey , before throwing a smoke bomb to disappear into the shadows.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who did King tell that he would return?",
                    "answer": "his father, Luisito Rey"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "When did Luisito Rey return to his father's side?",
                    "score": 0.89,
                    "answers": "his father , Luisito Rey will return!'will|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Luisito Rey do with a smoke bomb?",
                    "score": 0.8672,
                    "answers": "throwing a smoke bomb to disappear into the shadows|pcomp\ta smoke bomb|dobj\tto disappear into the shadows|advcl\tinto the shadows|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Luisito Rey's relationship with the King?",
                    "score": 0.7621,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com reported on 05/06/2018 that ' You have won this time , but his father , Luisito Rey will return!'will|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "At the end of the chapter, his father, Luisito Rey will arrive at secret lair, where his father, Luisito Rey will meet boss, The Tabasque√±o Messiah, who will kill his father, Luisito Rey for not being able to stop Jose Antonio Meade, candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What coalition did Jose Antonio Meade belong to?",
                    "answer": "Todos coalition"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Where did Luisito Rey meet The Tabasque√±o Messiah?",
                    "score": 0.815,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com reported on 05/06/2018 that At the end of the chapter , his father , Luisito Rey will arrive at secret lair , where his father , Luisito Rey will meet boss , The Tabasque√±o Messiah , who will kill his father , Luisito Rey for not being able to stop Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico|ROOT\tthat At the end of the chapter , his father , Luisito Rey will arrive at secret lair , where his father , Luisito Rey will meet boss , The Tabasque√±o Messiah , who will kill his father , Luisito Rey for not being able to stop Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico|ccomp\tfor Mexico|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Luisito Rey and Jose Antonio Meade?",
                    "score": 0.6662,
                    "answers": "who will kill his father , Luisito Rey for not being able to stop Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Luisito Rey's relationship with The Tabasque√±o Messiah?",
                    "score": 0.6374,
                    "answers": "his father , Luisito Rey|nsubj\tLuisito|compound\this father , Luisito Rey|nsubj\tLuisito|compound\this father , Luisito Rey|dobj\tLuisito|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Jose Antonio Meade and Luisito Rey?",
                    "score": 0.6298,
                    "answers": "to stop Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is The Tabasque√±o Messiah?",
                    "score": 0.6277,
                    "answers": "boss , The Tabasque√±o Messiah , who will kill his father , Luisito Rey for not being able to stop Jose Antonio Meade , candidate of the Todos coalition for Mexico|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "They also want to modify the end of the series, so that it will be located in the present and be a concert of Luis Miguel in the closing of Meade's campaign.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Whose concert will be held at the end of Meade's campaign?",
                    "answer": "Luis Miguel"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did Meade want to modify the ending of the series?",
                    "score": 0.8895,
                    "answers": "that They also want to modify the end of the series , so that it will be located in the present and be a concert of Luis Miguel in the closing of Meade 's campaign|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of Meade's campaign?",
                    "score": 0.7769,
                    "answers": "in the closing of Meade 's campaign|prep\tthe closing of Meade 's campaign|pobj\tof Meade 's campaign|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of Meade's campaign?",
                    "score": 0.7017,
                    "answers": "Meade 's|poss\tMeade 's campaign|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Meade and Luis Miguel?",
                    "score": 0.692,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tThey|nsubj\talso|advmod\tto|aux\tthe|det\tof the series|prep\tthe|det\tthe series|pobj\t,|punct\tso|mark\tthat|mark\tit|nsubjpass\twill|aux\tbe|auxpass\tin the present|prep\tthe|det\tand|cc\ta|det\tof Luis Miguel|prep\tLuis|compound\tthe|det\t's|case"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "There is still no response from producers.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the response from producers on 05/06/2018, according to www.eldizque.com?",
                    "answer": "no response"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Is there still no response from producers to the claims made by the website?",
                    "score": 0.9052,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com reported on 05/06/2018 that There is still no response from producers|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many producers have responded to Eldizque.com?",
                    "score": 0.8307,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}